Guide to the Sophocles Papas papers, 1900-1998
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: 1999 Accession
  - Enrique Granados (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Two Spanish dances: 1. Fandango No. 3, 2. Rondalla Aragonesa No. 6
  - Enrique Granados (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Valses poeticos
  - Eduardo Grau (Box 8, Folder 43)
    La fuente de Nie Pastrie
  - Eduardo Grau (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Greece - collections
  - Greece - methods (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Greece - orchestral (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Greece - solos (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Greece - songs (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Greek club date handbook: songs and dances every musician should know (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Greek songs and dances including music history of Greece (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Arranged by Kleon Raptakis
  - Harold Bellman (Box 8, Folder 35)
    Folk tune fugue for two guitars
  - Thomas Enoch Greene (Box 5, Folder 21)
    A method for practicing scales for guitar
  - Greensleeves (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Greensleeves (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Edvard Grieg (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Peasant's song and waltz, Op. 12
  - Edvard Grieg (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Solvejg's song (from the Peer Gynt Suite No. 2)
  - John R. Griggs (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - John R. Griggs (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Position etudes for plectrum guitar
  - Franz Gruber (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Silent night
  - Jao Guimaraes (Box 8, Folder 41)
    Sounds of bells
  - Guitar and lute Nos. 7, 16, 17, 21, 1978, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 22-25)
  - Guitar folio No. 1 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - The guitar newsletter, November 1968 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Guitar review Nos. 1-3, 5-8, 10-16, 18-20, 22-28, 1946-1956, 1958-1963, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 1-24)
  - Guitar review Nos. 29-33, 35-42, 1966, 1968-1974, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 1-13)
  - Guitar review Nos. 43-46, 48, 50-54, 61, 1978-1979, 1981-1983, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 1-11)
  - Guitar teaching in the United States: the life and work of Sophocles Papas (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Guitar transposer wheel and Nick Manoloff's modern accompaniment guide (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - The guitarist's hour: Book 1 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - The guitarist's hour: Book 2 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Guitarra magazine, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 19-20)
  - George Frederick Handel (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Air, Alegretto, Miuet, Passepied - arranged by Len Williams
  - George Frederick Handel (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Concerto in A major
  - George Frederick Handel (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Handel for the guitar, arranged by Leon Block
  - George Frederick Handel (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Siciliana
  - George Frederick Handel (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Suite in D minor
  - Leonard Handler (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - W. C. Handy (Box 1, Folder 27)
    East Saint Louis, arranged by Harry Volp and Frank Victor
  - W. C. Handy (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Loveless love, arranged by Harry Volp and Frank Victor
  - W. C. Handy (Box 1, Folder 30)
    The Memphis blues, arranged by Harry Volpe
  - W. C. Handy (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Saint Louis blues, arranged by Harry Volpe and Frank Victor
  - W. C. Handy's famous blues for the Hawaiian guitar (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Arranged by John Martell
  - W. C. Handy (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Yellow dog blues
  - John R. Hansen (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Hanuka, Oh Hanuka: The Hebrew "Christmas Season" song (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Arranged by Alexander Matos
  - Albert Harris (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Richard C. Harrison (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Hastings (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Rock of ages
  - Lorina Havill (Box 6, Folder 17)
    You can sight read: Book 1
  - Joseph Haydn (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Andante and menuet
  - Joseph Haydn and Francisco Tarrega (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Joseph Haydn (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Minuet, arranged by Jack Duarte
  - Opal Louise (Box 2, Folder 7)
    One hand waltz
  - Hebrew songs for the young pianist (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Hendley-Kaspar School of Musical Art, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Bruno Henze (Box 6, Folder 2)
    The classical guitar
  - Bruno Henze (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Kleine ouverture
  - Paul C. Herfurth (Box 6, Folder 3)
    A tune a day: the teacher's manual for violin instruction in group, public school classes or individual lessons
  - The "highwayman" and 12 other folk songs (Box 9, Folder 31)
    Arranged by Elisabeth Papas Smith
  - Holy communion (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Home study course (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Home study lessons for the Hawaiian guitar: lessons from 1 to 96 (Box 5, Folder 8-14)
  - F. Horetsky (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Adagio
  - Tobias Hume (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Sweet music: the Earl of Salusbury's favorite
  - Engelburt Humperdinck (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Hansel and Gretel suite
  - Hungary - collection (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Hungary - methods (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Incomplete and unplaceable music (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Intermediate guitar solos with commentary (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Arranged by Ada Richter
  - International Christmas for piano (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - International songs for guitar (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Arranged by Mel Bey
  - Italy - collections (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Italy - journals, 1959, 1964, 1974, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Italy - methods (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Italy - solos (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Italy - songs (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Italy - technical studies (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - J. Ivanovici (Box 9, Folder 29)
    Danube waves
  - Japan - collections (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Japan - collections (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Japan - journals, 1954-1956, 1957-1959, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 2-4)
  - Japan - methods (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Japan - programs (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Japan - solos (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Japan - songs (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Johnson (Box 1, Folder 71)
    Carman's whistle, arranged by Kojiro Kobune
  - James P. Johnson and Andy Razaf (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Aintcha got music, arranged by Harry Volpe and Frank Victor
  - John Johnson (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Galiarde
  - Scott Joplin (Box 1, Folder 46)
    The entertainer, arranged by Ada Richter
  - Journal of the American Musicological Society Vol. V, No. 3; Vol. VI, No. 1; Vol. VII, No. 3; Vol. VIII, No. 1; Vol. XIV, Nos. 1 and 3, 1952-1955, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 13-18)
  - Journal of the Lute Society of America, Inc., Vol. 1, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Journal of the Lute Society of America, Inc., Vol. X, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Joy to the World (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Jumping at the Woodside (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Dmitri Kabalevsky (Box 18, Folder 4)
    A little song
  - Larry Kaelin (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Brazilian breakdown
  - Don Keefer (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Kemp's jig and Playfellow jig (Box 1, Folder 72)
    Arranged by Kojiro Kobune
  - Kemp's jig (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - W. C. Kentner (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Recognisable blues
  - Kingston Trio (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Close up
  - L. Knipper (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Poliushko polie (Meadowland), arranged by Vladimir Bobri and V. Gabaeff
  - Barry Kornfeld (Box 6, Folder 7)
    The folk buitarist's manual: American folk buitar techniques and songs
  - Leo Kraft (Box 1, Folder 59)
    A new song
  - Fritz Kreisler (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Rondino (on a theme from Beethoven)
  - Joseph Kuffner and Walter Gotze (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - La barca (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - La paloma (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - G. L. Lansing (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Excelsior method for the banjo
  - Arthur Larson (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Latin Americana for the elementary pianist (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Arranged by F. Henri Klickmann
  - Augustin Lauro (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Two Venezuelan pieces for guitar: 1. Valse criollo, 2. Pavana
  - Newton C. S. Leao (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Ernesto Lecuona (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Siboney
  - Luigi Legnani (Box 1, Folder 84)
    Thirty-six caprices
  - Luigi Legnani (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Walzer, Op. 250, No. 6
  - Irmgard Lehrer-Carle (Box 8, Folder 5)
    25 folk-songs with guitar chords
  - Gene Leis (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Instruction chord book for guitar
  - Edwin H. Lemare (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Andantino, arranged by Edmund Severn
  - Arthur Levering (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Franz List (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Two short pieces arranged by Sophocles Papas
  - A little treasury of classics: Three (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A little treasury of classics: Four (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The little treasury of folksongs and dances: One (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Arranged by Cecily Lambert
  - Miguel Llobet (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Irene Lorence (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Spitfire McKenney new quick learning system
  - Lute Society of America newsletter Vol. XIV, No. 4; Vol. XVI, No. 2, 1979, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
  - Laura P. McCartney and Margaret R. Pabst (Box 5, Folder 18)
    Interval and chords: how to use them
  - Paquita Madriguera (Box 8, Folder 45)
    Two pieces
  - Ivor Mairants (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Method for 12 string guitar
  - Ivor Mairants (Box 5, Folder 16)
    The simplicity tutor for Spanish guitar
  - Sasha Makaroff (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Gypsy tango, arranged by Vladimir Bobri and V. Gabaeff
  - Kingston Trio (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Make way
  - Mandolin and guitar collection No. 9 - first mandolin or violin (Box 1, Folder 88)
    Arranged by Louis Tocaben
  - Mandolin and guitar collection No. 9 - second mandolin or violin (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Manual for the guitar (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
    Unidentified and incomplete
  - Manuscript - guitar album (Box 39)
  - Manuscripts - miscellaneous, titled (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Manuscripts - miscellaneous, untitled (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - N. Manzaros (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Ethnikos ymnos (Greek national hymn)
  - March (from the Baltic Lute Book, 1740) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Arranged by Jack M. Smith, Jr.
  - Franco Margola (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Eight pezzi facili per chitarra (Eight easy pieces for guitar)
  - Marine's hymn (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - John E. Marlow (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Heinrich Marschner (Box 1, Folder 82)
    12 bagatellen
  - Jack Marshall (Box 6, Folder 12)
    The art of the finger style guitar
  - Jules Massenet (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Elegia
  - Jules Massenet (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Jules Massenet (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Margery McHale (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Grasshoppers
  - Felix Mendelssohn (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Consolation: song without words
  - Nilo Menendez (Box 1, Folder 81)
    Aquellos ojos verdes (green eyes), arranged by Jorge Oller
  - J. K. Mertz (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Abendlied, Op. 13, Nr. 2; Adagio, Op. 13, Nr. 10; Kindermarchen, Op. 13, Nr. 8; Tarantella, Op 13, Nr. 6
  - J. K. Mertz (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Methods and teaching aids (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Jeffrey Meyerriecks (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Canonic variations on the names "Sophocles and Mercia"
  - Jeffrey Meyerriecks (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Four preludes: 1. August, 2. Fantasy on a child's song, 3. Burlesque, 4. Images
  - Luis Milan (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Luis Milan (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Pavane II
  - Luis Milan (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Six pavanas
  - Luis Milan (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Villancico
  - Minstrel songs with guitar accompaniment (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous front and back covers (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous lyrics, notes, etc. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous sheet music (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Rev. Ian Douglas Mitchell (Box 2, Folder 24)
    An American folk song mass
  - S. Molinaro (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Fr. Molino (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Rondo, Op. 28
  - J. Munoz Molleda (Box 8, Folder 42)
    Diferencias sobre un tema
  - James L. Molloy (Box 1, Folder 17)
    The Kerry dance, arranged by Maxwell Eckstein
  - James L. Molloy (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Monk - Abide with me (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Merle Montgomery (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Music theory papers: eye and ear training for the beginner
  - Merle Montgomery (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Music theory papers, third set, sight and sound
  - Montoya, his guitars, his triumphs, and his sorrows, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Moody Blues (Box 3, Folder 27)
    In search of the lost chord
  - Moonlight in Vermont (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Jack Moore (Box 5, Folder 17)
    Music for the guitar
  - Peter, Paul and Mary made easier for guitar (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - James Moran - correspondence (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Philip Morimitsu (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Thomas Morly (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Pavin
  - Modest Moussorgsky (Box 9, Folder 4)
    The old castle (from Pictures at an Exhibition)
  - Modest Moussorgsky (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Minuet from Ein Kleine Nachtmusik
  - Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (Box 1, Folder 80)
    Sonata No. 3, arranged by David Alzofon
  - Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Sonata theme
  - Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Symphonic skeleton scores: No. 6 in G minor
  - Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Theme from G minor symphony
  - Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Two easy pieces: Allegretto in C; Country dance
  - Alonso Mudarra - Fantasia (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Alonso Mudarra - Gallarda (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Santiago de Murcia (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Suite in D major
  - Marvin W. Muse (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Music studio news Vol. 11, No. 6, November 1954 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Music studio news Vol. 13, Nox. 3-4; Vol. 14, Nos. 1-4, 6, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 15-21)
  - My lord strange his galiarde (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Antonio Nava (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Allegro, Op. 51, Nr. 11
  - Antonio Nava (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Andantino
  - Cesare Negri (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Bianco fiore
  - Allan Neidle (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Netherlands - journals, 1950 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Netherlands - solos (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Netherlands - songs (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Netherlands - technical studies (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Ethelbert Nevin (Box 1, Folder 34)
    The rosary, arranged by H. F. Odell
  - Elizabeth Newman, editor (Box 5, Folder 2)
    The beginner's own book: folk songs carefully graded for ear-training, sight-singing, harmonization and transposition
  - Hans Newsidler - Jew's dance (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - J. Niles - Go way from my window (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Arranged by S. S. Cecil
  - 1978 stock order blank: a selected list of outstanding publications from the catalogs of Belwin-Mills Publishing Corp., Edward B. Marks Music Corp., MCA Music, a division of MCA, Inc. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Nineteenth century guitar music: Book 1 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    Arranged by John Hoffman
  - Wilhelm Nisters (Box 19, Folder 30)
    Karntner Volksweise
  - No se emendard jamas (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Johnny Noble and Gordon Beecher (Box 1, Folder 12)
    A song of old Hawaii, arranged by D. Savino
  - Nocturne (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Notes: the quarterly journal of the music library association, 1961-1964 (Box 10, Folder 19-23)
    Second series, Vol. XVIII, No. 4; Vol. XIX, Nos. 1 and 4; Vol. XX, No. 2; Vol. XXI, No. 3
  - Notes: the quarterly journal of the music library association, Vol. XXIII, No. 3, March 1967 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Oahu "rhythm style" note course for plectrum guitar (octave notation) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Herbert Forrest Odell (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Odell method for the mandolin
  - Old McDonald had a farm (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Bob Oort - Six sevillanas for Spanish guitar (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bob Oort - Six studies for classical guitar in the keys of C major and A minor (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Operatic album for guitar (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bret Orton (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Niccolo Paganini (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Niccolo Paganini (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Grand sonata
  - Niccolo Paganini (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 9, Folder 27)
    American fantasy: a medley for tenor banjo solo
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Biographical and genealogical information
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 8, Folder 40)
    The complete tremolo book for the guitar
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 38, Folder 17)
    Correspondence
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Lists of archival materials re: Sophocles Papas
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Manuscripts
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Manuscripts - "Method for classic guitar"
  - Sophocles Papas memorial service, March 8, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 9, Folder 40-41)
    Method for the classic guitar: new revised and enlarged edition
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Method for classic guitar: Vol. 1 primer
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Miscellaneous pamphlets
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Miscellaneous writings
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Papas' flamenco solo for guitar
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Six easy flamenco variations
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Sylvia waltz
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Wedding announcement - Sophocles Papas to Mercia F. Lorentz
  - Mitchell Parish (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Stars fell on Alabama
  - Part-songs for mixed voices (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Passantino Printing Co. - corporate papers (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Stephen Paulus (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Two moments
  - Pavana (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Personal (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Peter, Paul and Mary album (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Peter, Paul and Mary on tour (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Phonograph records (Box 27)
  - Alice Artzt (Box 40, Folder 80)
    Photograph
  - Carlos Barbosa-Lima, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Carlos Barbosa-Lima, early 1970s (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Carlos Barbosa-Lima, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - Carlos Barbosa-Lima, undated (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - Carlos Barbosa-Lima, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 81)
  - Carlos Barbosa-Lima, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 84)
  - Carlos Barbosa-Lima, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Carlos Barbosa-Lima, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Carol Bistyga, undated (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Herb Block, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Vladamir Bobri (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - John Boda (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Dr. Bray (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Dr. Braye, ca. 1961 (Box 40, Folder 89)
  - Charlie Byrd (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Charlie Byrd (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Charlie Byrd (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - Charlie Byrd (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Olga Coelho (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Martin de oede (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Dorothy Perrenoud de Goede (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Dorothy Perrenoud de Goede (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Gathering at Papas's home on Wynford Dr., 1970 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Arthur Godfrey (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Greek relatives (Box 40, Folder 83)
  - Guitar shop on 1816 M St., 1956 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Sharon Ibsen, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Sharon Ibsen, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 84)
  - Marcelle Jones (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Marcelle Jones (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - Alex La Goya (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Alex La Goya (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Alex La Goya (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - George Lorentz (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - John Marlowe (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Francisco Mignone (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - Miscellaneous photographs (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - George Lorentz (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - John Marlow (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - Francisco Mignone (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - Francisco Mignone (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous photographs (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Leonore Lorentz Myers (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - Negatives (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Joe Orso, ca. 1961 (Box 40, Folder 88-89)
  - Konstantina Papadopoulos, 1934 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Thomas Papadopoulos, 1934 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Papadopoulos, ca. 1905 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - David Papas, early 1970s (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - David papas, undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Elisabeth Papas, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Elisabeth Papas, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Elisabeth Papas, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Elisabeth Papas, 1951 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Elisabeth Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - Eveline Jessie Hurcum (Monico) Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Eveline Jessie Hurcum (Monico) Papas, ca. 1920 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Eveline Jessie Hurcum (Monico) Papas, 1933 (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, ca. 1937 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas wedding, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, ca. 1940 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, early 1940s (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas in Greece, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 82)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 86)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 87)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, 1938 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Mercia Lorentz Papas, undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Sophocles Papas, ca. 1905 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Sophocles Papas, ca. 1914 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Sophocles Papas, ca. 1914-1918 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Sophocles Papas, ca. 1920s (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Sophocles Papas, ca. 1937 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Sophocles Papas wedding, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Sophocles Papas, ca. 1960s (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Sophocles Papas in the music studio at 1816 M St, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Sophocles Papas, ca. 1961 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Sophocles Papas in Madrid, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Sophocles Papas with family in Ioannina, Greece, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Sophocles Papas, early 1970s (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Sophocles Papas on his 80th birthday, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1970s (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Sophocles Papas in Greece, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Sophocles Papas with student, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - Judge at International Guitar Seminar in Porto Allegre, Brazil, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - Sophocles Papas (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - Sophocles Papas, ca. 1961 (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Sophocles Papas at Haines' Point, undated (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - Sophocles Papas, undated (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 87)
  - Sophocles Papas, ca. 1961 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1938 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Sophocles Papas, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 8)